<result type = "1"><item><itemID>1</itemID><name>Rope</name><desc>Allows you to enhance the dog's jaw, thus making it stronger</desc><str>1</str><time>02:20:00</time><price>500</price></item><item><itemID>2</itemID><name>Treadmill</name><desc>Train. Due to increase stamina, dog during a fight less tired, and thus at the end of the match it beats not become weaker</desc><endr>1</endr><time>02:20:00</time><price>500</price></item><item><itemID>3</itemID><name>Tire</name><desc>Comprehensive training of strength and endurance. Your dog will be applied more striking blows and impact force will be kept for longer during the battle</desc><str>1</str><endr>2</endr><time>02:40:00</time><price>500</price></item><item><itemID>4</itemID><name>Bungee</name><desc>Train mobility dog. Do you want to fight during the dog bowl inflicted more significant impacts, train agility</desc><dex>2</dex><time>04:00:00</time><price>500</price></item><item><itemID>5</itemID><name>Running with load</name><desc>Complicated strength training and endurance. This type of training is one of the mandatory for the fighting dogs</desc><str>3</str><endr>4</endr><time>03:00:00</time><price>790</price></item><item><itemID>6</itemID><name>The log</name><desc>Excellent strength training and agility. The dog should not just pick up a log, but also keep it</desc><str>4</str><dex>5</dex><time>03:00:00</time><price>920</price></item><item><itemID>7</itemID><name>Trench</name><desc>Training the muscles of the body. Digging dog uses almost every muscle group. Accordingly, it becomes stronger</desc><str>8</str><time>02:00:00</time><price>1900</price></item><item><itemID>8</itemID><name>pool</name><desc>Train. Sometimes fights last for hours, and the dog must be ready for this. Not only have the power you need to have great endurance</desc><endr>8</endr><time>02:00:00</time><price>1900</price></item><item><itemID>9</itemID><name>Dummy</name><desc>Train mobility. The dog should not simply grabbed, but stay on the mannequin. It's not easy to do. Exercising on a mannequin, a dog will be much easier during the battle to keep the dog in position and apply the more significant strikes</desc><dex>8</dex><time>02:00:00</time><price>1900</price></item><item><itemID>10</itemID><name>Instructor</name><desc>Comprehensive training of all indicators of a dog. After working with an instructor in the dog will rise and strength and agility and endurance.</desc><str>17</str><dex>18</dex><endr>23</endr><time>03:10:00</time><price>5400</price></item><item><itemID>11</itemID><name>Bandwidth prepyatstviyPolosa obstacles</name><desc>Training on the obstacle course. The band is specifically designed to train elite fighting breeds of dogs. Serious preparation and growth indicators dog guaranteed</desc><str>23</str><dex>28</dex><endr>21</endr><time>04:20:00</time><price>7800</price></item><item><itemID>12</itemID><name>Special Course</name><desc>Elite special rate. This course makes this monster of a dog. Only one-time passing special course gives great results, not to mention the fact that the rate can go several times</desc><str>34</str><dex>45</dex><endr>40</endr><time>07:30:00</time><price>12800</price></item></result>